<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
    <ModMetaData>
        <name>Kobolds of the Rim [Revived for 1.4]</name>
        <author>Goob and LimeTreeSnake... and Aedhix too!</author>
        <supportedVersions>
            <li>1.4</li>
        </supportedVersions>
        <packageId>Goob.Kobolds</packageId>
        <description>Kobolds of the Rim has been updated to RimWorld 1.4. This version doesn't have Biotech genes and things like that (as far as I'm aware), but you should be able to use KotR and Biotech together. Let me know if you have any problems with the mod.

I tried to get into contact with goobi or LimeTreeSnake for a week before publishing this myself. Hope you enjoy the long-awaited 1.4 update.
-- Aedhix

Originally made by goobi and LimeTreeSnake. Link: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2569480318&searchtext=kobolds+of+the+rim

Original description:

-------------------------------------

The mod nobody asked for has finally arrived, Kobolds have managed to land in the harsh world of RimWorld and they're ready to steal and loot to their heart's content. These feisty little lizards come in many different colors and are (probably) a worthy addition to any colony good or bad.


UPCOMING FEATURES IN PATCH 0.2
📦 FURNITURE
⠀⠀⠀⠀• Two beds, one leather & one stone.
⠀⠀⠀⠀• Seats and chairs.
⠀⠀⠀⠀• Decoration for your kobold clan.
⠀⠀⠀⠀• One or two traps for protection.
🧱 MATERIAL
⠀⠀⠀⠀• Bone material to build furniture / weapons & Armor.


This mod currently comes with 10 armor pieces & 5 weapons that can only be worn by Kobolds, on top of this, they can also equip any non-Kobold exclusive armor as well!


⚠️ What do kobolds offer, as a race?
here i will list some comparison to a normal human pawn!

• Can eat any food, even rotten things.
⠀⠀⠀⠀They can rarely however, get sick from rotten or bad food.
⠀⠀⠀⠀This includes other kobolds.
• Hauls less.
• Moves faster.
• Very bad at researching.
• Very bad at medical.
• Will be okay with sleeping on the ground.
• Recovers faster from disease.
• Doesn't care about a whole lot.
⠀⠀⠀⠀Won't feel bad for selling prisoners.
⠀⠀⠀⠀Won't even care about dead (or rotting) bodies.
⠀⠀⠀⠀Being naked is no big deal for a kobold
• Will wear anything, clothing is clothing no matter where it came from.


Q: Are you planning on adding more armors or weapons?
A: As of the time of this upload, no. But it might be a goal for the future.

Q: Will this be CE compatible?
A: I do not use CE, but feel free to make a patch for it if desired!


_____________________________

[WARNING]

This mod will soon be moved over to @ LimeTreeSnake's steam workshop, as he is the main programmer!
That way, it will be MUCH easier to fix and add in future content.

Don't fret if it disappears, i will keep this mod up with a "outdated" tag once that day comes and link to the new version!

Thank you all for being such grandiose supporters of the kobold way, may more kobold related content come!
(I heard we're getting new armours, oh oh hooo!) 
        </description>
        <modDependencies>
            <li>
                <packageId>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</packageId>
                <displayName>Humanoid Alien Races 2.0</displayName>
                <steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=839005762</steamWorkshopUrl>
            </li>
        </modDependencies>

        <loadAfter>
            <li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
            <li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
			<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Ideology</li>
            <li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Biotech</li>
            <li>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</li>
        </loadAfter>
    </ModMetaData>
